# Vadym Borshch REACT DEV



## Personal details



Vadym Borshch



19archenemy92@gmail.com



Kharkiv, Ukraine 61051 Kharkiv



B,C,C1,CE,C1E



Ukrainian



t.me/Borshche



linkedin.com/in/borshchik

# Skills

**JavaScript** 

Git

HTML5

CSS

React

**TypeScript** 

Redux

ES6+

RESTAPI

Next.js

Tailwind CSS

### **Profile**

At InCode Group, I worked for about a year, primarily developing websites using React and Next.js. Then, I joined the Defense Forces, where I served for almost two years. During that time, of course, I was focused on other duties and wasn't coding. After being discharged from the military, I returned to my previous job and am now in the process of refreshing everything I knew. I'm working with the same tech stack listed in my skills and planning to learn Node.js, as I aim to become a full-stack developer.

I'm looking for a company that will hire me and provide opportunities for growth. Working solo is fine, but having someone who can point out my code and explain what's wrong is much more beneficial.

From my side, I guarantee decency, punctuality, meeting deadlines, and bringing result to your team.

# Education

Diploma of Higher Education: Operation and Maintenance of Lifting, Transport and Road Machinery and Equipment

Kharkiv Automobile and Road College

# **Employment**

#### **React Developer**

InCode Group, Kharkiv, Ukraine

Website development

- Marketplace development
- Online casino development
- Real estate solutions etc.

#### Truck Driver

Jun 2019 - Apr 2021

Oct 2021 - Present

2011

AUTOLEGION, Czestochowa, Poland

- Cargo delivery
- Followed highway code and traffic laws throughout deliveries

#### **Truck Driver**

Jun 2016 - May 2019

PHU ELKOR, Poznan, Poland

- Supply of products
- Loaded and unloaded goods with attention to safety, preventing damage to merchandise and vehicle.

## Courses

#### Front-end development

2021

IT-KAMASURTA

Material UI / TailwindCSS

Zustand

# Languages

English

••••

Ukrainian

